import { quizzes } from './quizzes.js';

quizzes.push(
  {
    title: "Advanced Quranic Knowledge",
    level: 3,
    quiz: 1,
    questions: [
      { question: "Which surah is Meccan but middle of Quran?", options: ["Ya-Sin", "Mulk", "Fatiha", "Rahman"], answer: "Ya-Sin" },
      { question: "How many juz in Quran?", options: ["30", "20", "15", "40"], answer: "30" },
      { question: "How many rukus in Al-Baqarah?", options: ["40", "50", "60", "37"], answer: "40" },
      { question: "Which surah starts with Mu‑Mir?", options: ["Fussilat", "Shura", "Zukhruf", "Sad"], answer: "Fussilat" },
      { question: "Which surah ends with 'Salaamun Qawlam Mir Rabbir Rahim'?", options: ["Fussilat", "Shura", "Mulk", "Haqqah"], answer: "Fussilat" },
      { question: "Which surah is longest in Madani?", options: ["Al-Baqarah", "Al-Imran", "An-Nisa", "Al-Ma'idah"], answer: "Al-Baqarah" },
      { question: "What is the meaning of 'Rahman'?", options: ["Merciful", "Patient", "Just", "Generous"], answer: "Merciful" },
      { question: "Which surah is called Heart of Quran", options: ["Ya-Sin", "Ikhlas", "Fatiha", "Mulk"], answer: "Ya-Sin" },
      { question: "Which surah describes night journey of Prophet?", options: ["Isra", "Mi’raj", "Hijr", "Maryam"], answer: "Isra" },
      { question: "Which surah opens with 'Kun Fayakun' phrase?", options: ["Ya-Sin", "Maryam", "Sad", "Rahman"], answer: "Sad" }
    ]
  }
);
